1	(Sister Verda Louellen Harden)	This is the story about my sister- in-law, when she was smaller.

2	She would have nose bleeds quite often.

3	Brother Branham prayed for her.

4	He told her, he said, "Now don't be	running around looking at your nose the whole time,	trying to see it."

5	He said "You just	forget it, God will heal it."

6	My mother-in-law, she was doing ironing one day,

7	and she had one of these irons that was sort of,

8	real bright and you can look in	and see yourself.

9	She was ironing clothes,	and she got up close to the

10	ironing board where she was ironing,

11	and she was turning the head every which way

12	and said, "Hmmm."

13	Her mother said, "What are you doing?

14	Don't you remember what Brother Branham said?

15	Don't be trying to look in a mirror,

16	and you're trying to look in my iron."

17	And said, "Do what he said." 

18	And, do you know what?

19	She was healed. She didn't have no more nose bleeds.

20	I have another testimony of one of	the family, is with Linda Luellen.

21	It was my husband's	brother's little girl.

22	She had this big sore on top of her head,

23	and it went all the way around her head.

24	Oh, it was an awful	looking place on her head.

25	The doctor said she'd never have	hair. The whole top of her head	was a mess.

26	When Brother	Branham prayed for her,

27	he told her, now this is through prophecy,

28	"You will have your hair."	And she did!

29	And now I have,	about my mother-in-law,

30	and she had a stopped up ear.

31	We were at the Tabernacle, and I was sitting by her,

32	and Brother Branham... the Holy Spirit was calling different ones	out,

33	and he called her,

34	and said, "The Lord has healed your ears."

35	I was sitting right by her, and there was this power.	

36	I mean when the Holy Spirit is there	that close, you can really feel it.

37	And as she said, "As soon as he	said that, it was like a little ol' pea with a string on it."

38	And it went from her ear, and went on down

39	and it was gone.

