1	And we’d been married, oh, several months. 

2	After about a year, little Billy Paul come on the scene.

3	Oh, she almost died.

4	And how I walked up-and-down the floors when the little fellow was being borned.

5	And just as soon as he was born, I heard him cry, and I screamed;

6	I said, “Thank You, Lord, it’s a boy, and his name shall be called Billy Paul.”

7	Many of you know my son, Billy Paul.

8	His mother died when he was just a little baby.

9	And I packed him around. Nighttime, we couldn’t afford enough coal to keep fire, so we’d…

10	I’d put his bottle under my shoulder, like this, and keep it warm for him at nighttime.

11	When he’d wake up, crying for his mother, I’d put the bottle in his mouth.

12	And she asked me, when she was dying, “Always stick with Billy.”

13	And we’ve been real chums. 

14	And so everywhere I go, I take Billy, and he’s stuck with me.

15	I'd like to take this opportunity to greet you.

16	I don't get this opportunity much anymore.

17	As you get a little older, you can't do the

18	things that you used to do. You want to, and in your heart,

19	but one thing I want you to know is that I love you and I pray for you daily.

20	And I know that you pray for me, because that's why I'm here today.

21	Truly we are a blessed people, and I just want to take an

22	opportunity to say God bless you,

23	and over the many years that I have known you and have worked with you,

24	when Dad was here, and now in the work with Brother Joseph,

25	it's just an honor to call you my friend.

26	And you know, there are words you can't say, but I just trust this

27	little greeting will be a blessing to you, just to say

28	I love you and that you can feel it from your heart.

29	You know, Brother Branham so we could we could talk too much;

30	we could sing too much; we could shout too much; but we can never

31	pray too much. And each day... Brother Branham told me, said,

32	"When you come in the office, Billy, I want you to do my mail."

33	And I said, "Daddy, I don't even know how to turn on the typewriter."

34	He said, "The Lord will be with you. He told me He wants you to do that for me."

35	And I said, okay. He said, "No matter if you've got one letter

36	or you've got a thousand, the first thing you do is kneel down and pray,

37	lay your hands on the mail, and ask the Lord to help you that day."

38	And he said, "Don't you answer any Bible questions. Don't you answer for me.

39	If it's a question to me, you keep them, and when we get together the

40	next day, or that day, or whenever, you write down on the

41	envelope and I'll answer the questions. But no matter

42	where I am, you remember every day that you do the mail."

43	He said, "I'll be praying for you and God will be there with you.

44	Don't process the mail, just open one letter at a time.

45	And just think like you only have one letter to answer,

46	and then when you're through with that,

47	discard it and then get another one."

48	And that's what I've been doing for the last sixty years.

49	And it's been a great honor.

50	And I know I'm getting older now.

51	I'm not an old man, but I know I'm getting up there.

52	Soon I've got to go and be...

53	What we've all been waiting for, and  I believe that hour is so close at hand.

54	But I just want an opportunity to say I love you,

55	and I thank you for your love to me; your stand for this Word.

56	You know Brother Billy, I'm just talking to you from my heart.

57	I believe this is a one man Message. It's a perfect Message.

58	There's no mistakes. There's many voices, but for me and my house, we only

59	follow one Voice, and that's the Voice of God to us in this day.

60	It's perfect and needs no interpretation. It interprets itself.

61	And I was thinking, a couple of days now I'll be getting my eighty-third birthday,

62	and in my heart and in my body, I don't feel that old.

63	I know I look it. The wife says I act like it, no I should say that.

64	If it wasn't for her I wouldn't even be here today.

65	But it's just the idea of being able to express yourself.

66	This Message is everything to me.

67	It's perfect. And may God encourage your heart to stay with it.

68	There's things we don't understand, but remember, if God thought it,

69	Brother Branham spoke, we believe it, and that settles it.

70	I was thinking the other day when I woke up,

71	and when I was just a little boy, I was about twelve years old,

72	and we was over in a little town called Vandalia Illinois,

73	and Brother Branham was having a tent meeting,

74	and we stayed a little cheap hotel, and I say that to go with my testimony here.

75	I know you've probably heard me give this testimony,

76	but maybe just one more time, I want to share it with you because

77	it's one of the greatest experiences of my life.

78	In this room, it didn't even have a bathroom, the bathroom was down the hall,

79	and we just had a wash basin right where the camera is here,

80	and it was just a little wash basin and a little pitcher.

81	And that's where we'd wash our hands. When we had take a shower,

82	take a bath, we'd go down at the end of the hall.

83	I used to sell in the meetings; I had little apron, and I'd go down and sell the little books.

84	There were three books Brother Branham had:

85	"Jesus Christ The Same Yesterday, Today, and Forever.

86	"I Was Not Disobedient To The Heavenly Vision. "Divine Healing. Healing In Campaigns."

87	And I thought I was something, get out there and sell those books.

88	Daddy would always... And I'd see the Lord moving in the meetings.

89	And as a kid he'd tell us about these things and how the

90	Angel would meet him. And I remember one night in this hotel room,

91	we were sitting there, and my dad's brother was working with us at that time.

92	He was driving a truck, and his name was Donny,

93	and he was the youngest of the brothers. He and I and Dad

94	were sleeping in the same room.

95	And I don't remember... I know Dad says on tape that he took

96	a pillow and threw over, and woke me up. All I remember, I woke up

97	and there was a pillow across my face.

98	He had this pillow across my face, and he says, "Paul."

99	I said, "Yes Sir?" It was about two o'clock in the morning.

100	And he said, "You know the Angel that Daddy talks about?" I said, "Yes sir."

101	And he said, "He visited me tonight and was telling me some things,

102	and about the meetings, and how to conduct the meetings,

103	and what was going to happen." And I said, "Yes Sir."

104	And he still had the pillow across my face. And he said, "And I asked Him, could I wake you up?"

105	and could I wake up my brother Donny?"

106	And he said, The Angel said, "You can wake you up Billy."

107	And he said, "Can he see you?" And the Angel said, "Yes."

108	He said...

109	Excuse me...

110	He said, "When Dad takes this pillow from your face,

111	you know where the wash basin is over there?" And I said, "Yes Sir."

112	He said, "He'll be standing there, and you can see Him."

113	I said, "Okay."

114	Remember, I was just twelve years old.

115	He took the pillow from my face, and I thought it would be an Angel with wings, flying around, but it wasn't like that.

116	There stood a Man in that room, dressed in pure white.

117	And He had His arms folded like this. His hair down to his shoulders.

118	He just stood there. One thing that was so outstanding to me,

119	He never spoke a word, but He'd look around the room, but his eyes

120	were totally focused on my dad.

121	Every move was watching my dad, and I can see them yet now,

122	them eyes just go around the room. He'd look at me, and he'd

123	look at my uncle, and he'd look back around like that. He'd move

124	His head a little bit, but His eyes never left Daddy's eyes.

125	And I grabbed Daddy, because I didn't know. It was a Man standing

126	in the room over by the window.

127	And I'll never forget, Daddy told me, "Don't be scared, son

128	He's sent from the presence of Almighty God.

129	He won't harm you

130	He'll be a blessing."

131	Now watching... held real close, Daddy held me, and He

132	went from that Being of a Man, just as Brother Branham describes Him, into,

133	I'm not going to say a pillar fire, it was like a mist, a light, a vapor.

134	He just kind of vanished, and He went out the window, right out of the room like that.

135	And when He left, a rainbow came right in the same window

136	and hung in that room for hours. At midnight, two o'clock in the morning,

137	dark room, but He stood there and that pillar of... excuse me, that rainbow stayed in the room,

138	I felt a presence.

139	And I asked my dad later, "Why did that happen?"

140	And he said, "Because I wanted you to see Him.

141	God called you to work with me, Billy, and

142	I wanted you to see Him and to know what Daddy was telling you was the truth.

143	Not that I doubt it, but it was just such an experience,

144	such a wonderful experience. And all through my life, I traveled,

145	and my job was to get Daddy in and out of the meetings, you know.

146	Sometimes I let him stay too long, sometimes I'd take him too quick,

147	you know. But I kept doing what he said,

148	and I'd give out the prayer cards, and I'd bring the people up to him,

149	and sometimes I let him stay too long, and he'd say,

150	"Billy, you let me stay too long tonight.

151	Tomorrow night, don't give out prayer cards because Dad's too tired."

152	I'd go home, and I'd cry, and be so upset because I messed up the next night's meeting.

153	And sometimes I'd take him too quick. He'd say, "You could've let me stay a little longer."

154	And, oh, it was just a hard time. But what a wonderful time!

155	I've seen the people that just any disease...

156	I was thinking the other night...

157	You know, you watch the news, they call this disease that, and they change the name,

158	but it's all the devil. It's all the devil.

159	But when the Angel met him, He said, "If you get the people to believe you,

160	nothing will stand before your prayer, not even cancer."

161	And I'm a witness to you today,

162	that He's the same yesterday, today, and forever,

163	and not one time, from that time in that room when I saw that Angel,

164	that I could always tell you, not Brother Billy, but that presence.

165	I could tell when He was near,

166	even before Daddy would say, "You know what I'm waiting for, Something..."

167	I might be down in the audience working of the prayer line,

168	ushering, whatever I might be doing,

169	but I could tell exactly when that Angel came to the platform.

170	Before Dad sometimes even said, "He's here," I knew He was!

171	So it didn't make a difference what diseases was, I knew when they left they

172	were going to be well. But He said, "If you get to people to believe you..."

173	And I was telling someone the other day,  I said, I've seen them bring them in well,

174	and they sat there and make fun,

175	and they packed them out, dead.

176	I've seen them pack them out paralyzed,

177	and I've seen them bring them in on a stretcher, and they would be dead,

178	and I've seen them walk out alive and well. Only believe.

179	So I just wanted to say, God bless you.

180	And I like to just leave my little greetings to you and this:

181	If I don't see you in person, I'll meet you on that day.

182	And I had the privilege when he was here,

183	to have the interviews for him, to set them up. I don't know how

184	how it's going to be over there; I just know I'm going to be there, by His Grace.

185	And I say, God blessed me above any man.

186	First of all He let me be His son.

187	He chose me.

188	Then He let me be a son of a prophet

189	and to be a brother of a prophet.

190	And to have worked with both of the prophets in my lifetime.

191	Truly, I have been a blessed man.

192	All we have to do is push play

193	and obey.

194	God bless you and remember, if God thought it, Brother Branham spoke it,

195	 I believe it, and that settles it. God bless you.

