Brother Jerry Amalong
Part 3
“Christianity is living for others”


1	00:00:02:09	“Christianity is living for others”

2	00:00:05:07	I can't think of what year it was. My wife was with me

3	00:00:09:06	on one of our trips; we went to Cuernavaca.

4	00:00:11:14	Cuernavaca is a town below Mexico City.

5	00:00:15:22	Brother General Medina Estrella

6	00:00:20:11	is the general that helped Brother Branham get into Mexico.

7	00:00:25:06	I got his name and address in Cuernavaca, and we went to see him.

8	00:00:30:18	He was telling about different ones,

9	00:00:33:02	how they had to let Brother Branham down

10	00:00:36:22	with a rope behind the back of the platform.

11	00:00:43:16	He told about the little dead baby being raised to life,

12	00:00:50:07	and the blind man that didn't have any shoes, healed.

13	00:00:55:09	He said, “Brother Branham prayed for so many people…”

14	00:00:59:20	He couldn’t point them out fast enough.

15	00:01:03:04	So when we had gone down there and showed Brother Branham films

16	00:01:06:18	years later

17	00:01:08:15	to some of those churches, different ones told about being

18	00:01:11:22	healed in Brother Branham’s meetings. One of them, she said her

19	00:01:16:12	and another woman were dying with TB, and she Brother Branham

20	00:01:20:21	pointed them out and told them they were,	"Thus Saith the Lord" healed,

21	00:01:24:17	and from that night on, “We were healed.”

22	00:01:29:00	During those meetings, he (General Medina) said that after Brother	Branham left,

23	00:01:32:18	“People kept coming, and they got

24	00:01:36:13	there and found out Brother Branham had already gone.

25	00:01:40:16	Some of them had all kinds of diseases and sick.

26	00:01:44:19	They sat down on the rocks on the side of that

27	00:01:47:19	mountain, where he had those services.”

28	00:01:51:15	He (General Medina) said, “Brother all I can	say, evidently, the Angels of God we're still

29	00:01:58:23	in that place, because people started getting healed all

30	00:02:03:22	over the place. Even with Brother Branham gone,

31	00:02:07:03	that atmosphere and that presence was still there.”

32	00:02:11:20	He said, “Just testimony after testimony took place.”

33	00:02:15:07	But you know, Scripture says about being shod with the

34	00:02:19:13	Gospel of peace. Today, because of this Message,

35	00:02:25:23	we've been able to take that same Message to the people,

36	00:02:31:08	and give them a good pair shoes of the Gospel,

37	00:02:34:09	give them a coat to wear, give them	clothes, clothe them with the Word of God.

38	00:02:40:06	There was times I didn't have anything to work with.

39	00:02:45:00	Denomination would say, “You just join with us,	we will give you all the material you need."

40	00:02:48:18	Of course that wasn't the material I needed.

41	00:02:52:02	That was their attitude, but to see today

42	00:02:58:01	the material that is made available,

43	00:03:00:14	and back from the time that Brother Joseph took Voice of God over

44	00:03:05:10	and Spoken Word Publications,

45	00:03:07:12	and to see that material not just sit there, but sent out.

46	00:03:16:00	What's the use of having a gun without	ammunition? And that’s why I felt many times,

47	00:03:22:05	“I’ve got a rifle but no ammunition”

48	00:03:31:13	To finally start getting the material that we needed;

49	00:03:36:03	it made me rejoice because I had it to give to the people.

50	00:03:41:17	That’s what we are, a channel that God can work in and through.

51	00:03:45:03	It’s always an honor. Christianity is living for others,

52	00:03:48:22	and that's what I see the efforts of the Voice of God doing;

53	00:03:53:03	getting the books, the tapes, the CDs,

54	00:03:56:03	and you name it, into the hands of the ministers.

55	00:04:00:04	I know what it meant to me when I didn't have anything,

56	00:04:04:13	to receive it. I tell you what, I just...

57	00:04:11:14	There's not words to express…

58	00:04:14:12	There's not words to

59	00:04:18:00	give the gratitude,

60	00:04:21:00	the thanks to God and

61	00:04:23:19	Voice of God Recordings through Brother	Joseph, and Brother Billy Paul,

62	00:04:27:12	and you brothers that are giving your lives to print that

63	00:04:30:13	material. You print it, but without anything to work with

64	00:04:34:16	what could we do?

65	00:04:36:21	Of course,

66	00:04:39:19	somebody got behind you brothers,

67	00:04:42:14	and you brothers have got behind the work like you have…

68	00:04:47:22	I just thank God, the way I was raised on the ranch…

69	00:04:52:19	I've had hand-me-down clothes and all that, so we

70	00:04:57:13	take take a lot of clothing, besides

71	00:05:01:03	the religious material to the people down there.

72	00:05:04:15	I’ve seen people that didn't even have a change	of clothes, we’d take clothes to them.

73	00:05:08:02	It just does something to you. We just thank the Lord that

74	00:05:12:21	we can work with your brothers, like we have over

75	00:05:15:23	the years, appreciate what you've done, what you’re doing,

76	00:05:19:20	and we hold you in high esteem.

77	00:05:22:15	God bless you.

78	00:05:27:11	Thank you, Brother Amalong, for your many years of service, and	thank you for sharing your story with us.

