1	I got to go to the Tabernacle every time during the Seven Church Ages.

2	All seven of them, I got to be there, which I'm thankful for.

3	The last Church Age;

4	it wound up to the Seventh Church Age,

5	and he had preached his sermon.

6	All of a sudden this light,

7	he was winding up; this light

8	appeared on the back end of the church.

9	I was sitting up here in the front.

10	It would be about like

11	a big round circle, you know,

12	and it marked down the Church Ages; the light whether it was...

13	however he was telling about the Church Ages, it would mark it off.

14	I mean, it was something to see.

15	That's the first time I'd seen the supernatural light.

16	It's something different. I mean, you don't see things like this.

17	I mean... we didn't have no prophets in our day until

18	when Brother Branham started preaching, that's when it all came out,

19	which it was wonderful. I mean, it was wonderful to see

20	some of these things and

21	know that you got to see them yourself.

22	Well, is there a word that can really describe that man?

23	He was... I don't know if you've got any words in the English language

24	to really describe a prophet of God. 

25	Thank you Sister Verda for sharing your tesimonies and eye-witness accounts with us.

