1	Hey everybody.

2	What are you all doing in the memorabilia room?

3	I really like in here too.

4	Yeah, there's all kinds of Brother Branham stuff.

5	Hey, I've got a game. You want to play?

6	It's called “Trivia.”

7	You try to guess who I am with the clues I give you.

8	Yeah? Okay, let's do it. First clue.

9	I was related to Jesus.

10	Do you know who I am?

11	I'm pretty popular.

12	Not yet? Okay, I've got more clues. Let me look in my pocket here.

13	Mmmm, Okay here we go.

14	Elizabeth was my mom.

15	Do you know now?

16	All right. Well I could keep giving clues if you want.

17	Okay, the next one is pretty good.

18	Makes me kind of hungry.

19	Let’s see if it makes you hungry. You ready?

20	I ate grasshoppers and honey. Whoa, wow, grasshoppers and honey.

21	What a combo.

22	Okay, I'll give you some more clues. Here we go.

23	I was a preacher who preached in the wilderness.

24	Surely you know now.

25	Not yet?

26	Okay, my last clue is the biggest clue. I'm sure you'll get it.

27	I baptized Jesus.

28	Yeah, yeah, I did.

29	Yeah, you got it! Good job. I'm John the Baptist. Great job guys.

30	I knew you would get it.

31	It only took a few clues

32	All right, well, enjoy the time here. God bless you. Bye.

