1	I got another testimony about	Brother Taylor, here.

2	He was down at the Tabernacle.

3	He would help	people get a chair to sit down, as	long as there were chairs.

4	And so this particular day,	he was going to preach on something

5	that I really wanted to hear. And I was praying and I thought,

6	"Lord, I would like to be	inside, and I really want to hear this."

7	and I thought, "Well if I could	just get there and get in

8	where I could hear. I want to hear it so bad."

9	So I went in, the first thing I met was Brother	Taylor

10	He had a chair in his hand. A folding chair.

11	He said come on	I'll let you down.

12	So I went down through there

13	and guess where he put me,

14	right under Brother Branham's	elbow.

15	I couldn't have got no closer

16	at that time, after he was preaching and everything,

17	and this one woman came up. She	wanted this spirit cast off of her.

18	She had spells all the time.

19	And I knew the woman. She was going to	be prayed for by Brother Branham.

20	She came up there, he took his watch off,

21	I was up there, where I could really see.

22	He took his watch off and put it in his pocket

23	and I thought, "Well, what's he doing?"

24	He said, "I have lost a lot of crystals	out of my watch by casting out devils."

25	So he put his watch in his pocket,

26	and he prayed for the woman	and cast out the devil,

27	took his watch back out of his pocket and showed us.

28	it had a crack right across the crystal.

29	I was at Brother Branham's meetings.

30	When I first started to church,	I didn't have no where to go.

31	And we had a little church right there in Otisco.

32	About almost a mile	from my house, and I walked.

33	At this particular time, and after I started	going and got to know Brother Branham,

34	and I was in his meeting,

35	he preached on baptism in the Name of the Lord	Jesus Christ.

36	Well, I had to look all that up, because I had never	heard. But I had been baptised as a kid

37	in a Methodist church. The more I	heard, the more I knew I had to be baptised again.

38	and it spoke of the Holy Ghost,

39	well i never heard nothing about the	Holy Ghost, not in the Methodist church.

40	And then I heard of Brother Branham, got to meet him.

41	And I was in his meeting,

42	he asked us to stand to our feet,

43	the ones that wanted the Baptism	of the Holy Ghost.

44	I stood to my feet,

45	and when he spoke

46	it was like he spoke to me,

47	"You will receive the	Baptism of the Holy Ghost."

48	And then as time went on, maybe a	few days passed, I had went to

49	another one of the brother's meetings, I can't remember which one.

50	We had sister churches.

51	All of a sudden, he said, "All that wants the Baptism of	the Holy Ghost,

52	just walk up to the altar here."

53	Well I started shaking in my shoes, because I knew I wanted it,

54	and I knew Brother Branham told	me I would get it,

55	and I was standing and twisting around,

56	and finally, I felt like I	was going to die if I didn't move.

57	And when I did,

58	I did not take two or three... as soon as I	stepped out I think I got it.

59	It wasn't no time, the Holy Spirit fell on me.

60	And He's helped me all the days since.

