1	00:00:09:01	I am Jerry Amalong and this is my story.

2	00:00:14:02	Brother Branham lifted Jesus Christ so high,

3	00:00:17:18	that you couldn't see the man without	seeing Jesus Christ in the man.

4	00:00:24:22	There are no words to express…

5	00:00:28:25	Listen to that voice; listen to the Message of the hour and apply it	to your life.

6	00:00:34:12	Then it will become a part of you. Take time to pray.

7	00:00:37:28	Brother Jerry Amalong has served as a missionary to the people of	Mexico for over 60 years, 27 of those years were spent as the	official VGR distributor. He has spent countless days and nights	with some of the poorest people on Earth.

8	00:00:53:23	Only God knows how many souls have been touched by his desire to get	the Word of God to the hungry people of Mexico.  

9	00:01:03:15	Part 1 of 3	"That Holy Ghost Experience"

10	00:01:07:26	I was raised on a ranch up in the	Chiricahuas (Southern Arizona mountains).	I had three brothers and three sisters.

11	00:01:16:14	My dad had a ranch, raising about 40 head of cattle.

12	00:01:22:28	We had a fruit orchard.

13	00:01:28:22	Most of what we had was just a Sunday	school up there above the ranch.

14	00:01:35:20	They had Bible classes,

15	00:01:37:27	and we’d try to attend the Sunday School Union get togethers.

16	00:01:47:00	At the age of seventeen was when I had the Holy Ghost experience.

17	00:01:50:18	I had started to college.

18	00:01:52:24	We were at special services,

19	00:01:58:14	and the experience I had was that I spoke in pure Spanish for about	three, three-and-a-half hours.

20	00:02:07:24	When all that happened, I couldn’t speak English for some time.

21	00:02:12:02	One of the Spanish brothers came in and he said,

22	00:02:16:14	“That’s the purest Spanish I ever heard.”

23	00:02:19:26	Then I kept trying to speak English again,	and it still came out Spanish.

24	00:02:24:11	So after about three or three-and-a-half hours,

25	00:02:26:13	I finally got where I could speak English	again, and couldn’t speak Spanish.

26	00:02:33:01	As time went on,

27	00:02:36:13	it fell into my hands some of Jack Coe’s books and pamphlets,

28	00:02:43:17	and Voice Of Healing (magazine)

29	00:02:49:01	stories that had Brother Branham in it and different ones. I’d read	them

30	00:02:53:19	and I’d get inspired, and it made me want to become an evangelist.

31	00:02:58:05	During that time there was a John Wayne

32	00:03:01:26	movie being made out at Old Tucson, and they offered me

33	00:03:06:19	the job, somebody with a horse, for twenty-seven dollars a day.

34	00:03:10:09	Back then that was a lot of money,

35	00:03:13:10	so, I said well,

36	00:03:16:20	I just had that Holy Ghost experience, and I had second

37	00:03:20:09	thoughts about it, and I turned it down. Somebody said,

38	00:03:24:15	“You could have been rich and famous if you took that job.”

39	00:03:27:25	I said, “Well, thank the Lord I'm not rich and famous.”

40	00:03:32:04	I’m glad that I made the right decision, and from that time on I

41	00:03:38:22	started working with an evangelist that had a tent.

42	00:03:42:04	Of course, I slept inside the tent	to be kind of a guard, so to speak.

43	00:03:47:24	And we ended up going among

44	00:03:50:25	the Navajos and Apaches at that time,

45	00:03:56:00	and I had heard of Brother Branham,	but I never read much of his material.

46	00:04:02:18	We were sitting church one day, and I wasn’t asleep.

47	00:04:08:05	I had a vision and saw myself down in Mexico.

48	00:04:13:11	Well, I had fought a forest fire and hadn’t got paid for it.

49	00:04:17:26	I was out at my brother’s in the vision,

50	00:04:20:17	and I saw myself walking out to the mailbox, and I got the

51	00:04:25:06	forty dollar check from Uncle Sam (United States Government) for	fighting forest fires.

52	00:04:29:20	And then I saw myself down in Mexico, speaking.

53	00:04:33:11	Then I snapped out of it, and that's actually the way it happened.

54	00:04:39:27	Part 2 coming soon

