1	This little old lady, she just kinda walked the streets.

2	She wasn't too clean, she was kind of unkept.

3	She didn't know us. 

4	She told me and my mother,

5	"Willy Branham," called him "Willy,"

6	"Willy Branham's having a meeting tonight,

7	you've got to go down there." Well, we'd never heard of him.

8	I think we were going Nazarene

9	We found out where. She said, "it's Eighth and Penn Street"

10	She knew where it was at.

11	"Eighth and Penn Street. Gotta go." We went.

12	We never heard anything like that.

13	The church was full,  of course it was little.

14	I remember my little son, he's  passed away, 

15	he was little and fat,  he was about four years old,

16	and he sat on the altar. The kids did because there was no room,

17	but I just vividly remember that

18	and I thought I was going to see  a great big fella come out

19	I saw this little old humble fella come out, Brother Branham.

20	Oh, it was wonderful! Praise the Lord! Glory to God, Hallelujah!

21	I remember just as if it was yesterday, yes.  The very first time.

22	I was praying for my husband

23	that I wanted him to be a Christian.

24	I didn't tell him anything,

25	see, he just knew. He said, "Sister Ellen,

26	Don't you worry, your husband's going to become a Christian."

27	And my husband did  become a Christian after that,

28	but he didn't make no big to do to it, he just said that.

29	Well, my mother was praying for my neice.

30	She had TB. And that's been years and years ago,

31	and he said, "Sister Baker, don't you worry."

32	Now, she never asked for prayer.

33	He said, "Sister Baker, don't you worry,  your granddaughter is

34	going to be healed of that Tuberculosis."

35	He said, "She's going get out of there."  So, she did.

36	She worked in stores, and raise them kids, and lived to be

37	about eighty-nine years old.

