
Brother Jerry Amalong
Part 2

“Hunger among the people”



1	00:00:01:22	“Hunger among the people”

2	00:00:06:01	We finally had a few books or tracts to work with,

3	00:00:10:07	and I would find out where the “hallelujah church” is.

4	00:00:13:17	“Well, that hallelujah church is three	blocks that way, and two blocks that way.”

5	00:00:18:10	A lot of times there would be no pastor there,

6	00:00:20:06	but I would just leave a book or two, or tracts

7	00:00:24:02	and sow some seed.

8	00:00:29:19	If the pastor was there,

9	00:00:31:19	we would try to make arrangements to show the films.

10	00:00:35:00	And the first films we had were

11	00:00:37:16	one of Brother T.L. Osborn, and then we finally got

12	00:00:40:18	Deep Calleth To The Deep.

13	00:00:44:04	It would open a door for us to

14	00:00:48:11	have a service with them.

15	00:00:51:15	A lot them had heard of T.L. Osborn and never heard of Brother	Branham.

16	00:00:56:06	So we would show Brother Osborn’s film first, and tell how he

17	00:01:00:09	got his ministry under this prophet of God, named William Branham.

18	00:01:04:15	Then we would show Brother Branham's film.

19	00:01:09:05	It was testimony after testimony of churches

20	00:01:12:23	that embraced the Message, and wanted more	books, and wanted more material.

21	00:01:19:09	We were able to share with them

22	00:01:22:08	whatever was available at the time.

23	00:01:28:07	The glorious part about it is when you see hunger

24	00:01:32:03	among the people.

25	00:01:38:18	I had a little PA system fixed up on that

26	00:01:42:16	international wagon we used.

27	00:01:44:17	We’d drive around in a little village after we got permission to

28	00:01:51:05	show the films, and we’d announce, “Good Day,	Good Day! Free film!” (in Spanish)

29	00:01:58:16	“Come see this film tonight!”

30	00:02:01:01	There is a flat place

31	00:02:04:04	where they had parties,

32	00:02:05:11	and it wasn't anything to have

33	00:02:09:04	a couple hundred people. They would	bring their chairs and come sit and

34	00:02:15:19	we would show the films, and give out tracts and

35	00:02:18:15	whatever material we had available.

36	00:02:21:05	The first tapes I had, Allen Mosley loaned me an

37	00:02:25:22	old five-inch tape recorder,

38	00:02:32:04	and that was the first tapes I started	listening to of Brother Branham.

39	00:02:36:11	It put a hunger and a thirst in my heart.

40	00:02:39:06	I knew there was something different than any

41	00:02:43:19	other minister I had ever heard.

42	00:02:47:15	Brother Branham lifted Jesus Christ so high

43	00:02:50:05	that you couldn't see the man without	seeing Jesus Christ in the man.

44	00:02:58:02	The humility in Brother Branham, the way he prayed,

45	00:03:01:06	and the effect of his ministry, I thought, “No man ever spoke

46	00:03:05:13	like this man. No man ever lived like this man.”

47	00:03:08:18	I had been around a lot of different	elements that tried to copy that,

48	00:03:13:03	but Brother Branham lived the life, and all I can say is,

49	00:03:18:22	through hearing that voice, there was just something about it

50	00:03:23:01	that every time you put on a tape, you

51	00:03:26:12	couldn’t hardly wait to put on the next tape.

52	00:03:28:01	It certainly had a great effect on my life,

53	00:03:31:07	and later on, in my wife’s life. The first time we were in

54	00:03:36:21	Brother Branham's meetings, up in Phoenix,

55	00:03:40:16	Brother Carl Williams introduced Brother Branham,

56	00:03:44:05	and I don't know why in my mind, I had Brother Branham

57	00:03:47:10	pictured as a physically big man.

58	00:03:49:21	I guess because I'm tall and big, but when Brother Branham

59	00:03:53:14	came out, I was going…

60	00:03:56:14	I could just see the top of him above the pulpit.

61	00:04:00:10	Brother Carl Williams introduced Brother Branham, and

62	00:04:06:05	I don’t remember the first sermon we heard him preach,

63	00:04:09:19	but when he got up to speak, and before he got through,

64	00:04:13:16	I knew he was a big man. I went there praying for the meetings.

65	00:04:18:13	When I left, I was praying for me.

66	00:04:21:04	Amen.

67	00:04:23:20	You know, all I can say is when that ministry crosses your path,

68	00:04:29:23	you can never be the same person.

69	00:04:33:02	There was such an atmosphere.

70	00:04:37:10	One of the things that happened up in	Phoenix at one of the meetings,

71	00:04:41:07	there were probably, I’m guessing,

72	00:04:43:03	fifteen-hundred people there. I never will forget

73	00:04:46:22	one little sister, she had an evil spirit on her.

74	00:04:51:04	She started climbing over the

75	00:04:53:08	people in her row, saying, “Let me out of here! Let me out of here!”

76	00:04:57:21	She finally got out, and Brother Branham just bowed his head,

77	00:05:01:21	and he said, “Heavenly Father, send Your Holy Spirit after her.”

78	00:05:05:10	And she had gone out in the hall. In a	little bit, she came back in, sat down,

79	00:05:10:13	he prayed for her, and she was completely	delivered. It was an experience I

80	00:05:14:11	will never forget, to have seen that happen

81	00:05:18:16	and have been there to be a witness of it.

82	00:05:23:13	It was really something.

83	00:05:25:10	Part 3 coming soon

