1	From VGR Open House, Easter 2006 Part 3

2	The doctors told Mother she could die if she had another baby.

3	She asked Dad, "Do you think I'll die?" Daddy told her, "I don't know if you'll die,

4	but the baby's going to be born. You're going to have Joseph."

5	May 19th, 1955. I was born.

6	Isn't Mother's hair beautiful?

7	One day while riding in the car with my daddy,

8	I told him, "I sure like that preaching Daddy." He said "Well, I got one fan."

9	That was me!

10	Lois became a Branham

11	Daddy said, "Not because she's my daughter-in-law,

12	but she's one of the finest girls I know of. She's a dandy."

13	Now we can all see why Billy didn't like to take Lois fishing.

14	One day leaving a meeting, the Lord spoke to Daddy and said,

15	"Lois, you'll bare a son. The Lord has blessed you. Your female trouble is gone."

16	Little Paul was born nine months later.

17	One morning eating breakfast, Daddy had another vision.

18	He told Billy, he saw Lois feeding another baby.

19	Eleven months later, David was born.

