1	00:00:11:14	Daddy

2	00:00:20:21	Grandpa and Grandma Branham with Uncle Donnie and Aunt Dolores

3	00:00:28:09	The Branham boys in a swimming hole

4	00:00:30:21	Doc and Jesse in the water. Charles, Henry, and Donnie on the bank.

5	00:00:45:00	When Daddy was a young boy he fought in the Golden Gloves.

6	00:00:48:15	Then he went professional, and won fifteen straight fights.

7	00:00:52:12	He said the first night that met the Lord Jesus, that it finished his fighting career.

8	00:01:03:04	I love the story Daddy told about this picture of him killing a bear with his knife.

9	00:01:07:13	People would ask him, "Billy, wasn't you afraid of that bear?"

10	00:01:12:05	Nope. If I'd been afraid of him, he'd of killed me.

11	00:01:28:03	Sister Hope

12	00:01:32:19	When Daddy was about twenty three or twenty four years old, he met Hope.

13	00:01:37:02	He said she was a very lovely Christian girl with a sweet, humble character.

14	00:01:43:23	Daddy and Sister Hope on their honeymoon.

15	00:01:48:21	The young man with Daddy and Sister Hope is her brother.

16	00:01:52:06	If you look real close you will see the gun that is tucked in Daddy's pants.

17	00:01:56:04	In other words, "don't mess with me."

